<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kdenetwork_filesharing</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <name>Samba Filesharing Plugin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Connector per a l'intercanvi de fitxers a Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Samba-Modul zur Dateifreigabe</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Fitxategiak partekatzeko Samba plugina</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">'Plugin' de Partilha de Ficheiros do Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Samba fildelningsinsticksprogram</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Додаток оприлюднення файлів у Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSamba Filesharing Pluginxx</name>
  <summary>Adds Configuration of Samba sharing for folders in Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Afegeix la configuració d'ús compartit de Samba al Dolphin per a les carpetes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Einrichtung von Samba-Freigaben für Ordner in Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Dolphinen Samba bidez karpetak partekatzeko konfigurazioa gehitzen du</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Adiciona a configuração da partilha por Samba de pastas no Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Lägger till inställning av delning av kataloger i Dolphin med Samba</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Додає пункти налаштовування спільного використання тек Samba у Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxAdds Configuration of Samba sharing for folders in Dolphinxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>With this plugin you can set your folders to be shared on your local network using Samba, which talks the SMB protocol common on Windows and other platforms.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Amb aquest connector podreu establir les vostres carpetes perquè es comparteixin a la xarxa local usant Samba, el qual parla el protocol SMB comú al Windows i altres plataformes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit diesem Modul können Sie Ihre Ordner in Ihrem lokalen Netzwerk freigegeben. Dazu wird Samba mit SMB-Protokoll verwendet, das auf Windows und anderen Plattformen verbreitet ist.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Plugin honekin zure karpetak tokiko sarean Samba erabiliz partekatzeko ezar ditzakezu. Samba, Windows eta beste plataforma batzuetan ohikoa den SMB protokoloan mintzatzen da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Com este 'plugin', poderá configurar as suas pastas para ficarem partilhadas na sua rede local com o Samba, que por sua vez fala o protocolo SMB comum do Windows e das outras plataformas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Med det här insticksprogrammet kan du ställa in kataloger att delas på det lokala nätverket genom att använda Samba, vilket använder SMB-protokollet gemensamt med Windows och andra plattformar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою цього додатка ви можете налаштувати ваші теки на спільне використання у локальній мережі за допомогою Samba, системи обміну даними протоколом SMB, який є поширеним протоколом у Windows та на інших платформах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxWith this plugin you can set your folders to be shared on your local network using Samba, which talks the SMB protocol common on Windows and other platforms.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dolphin</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdenetwork-filesharing/kdenetwork-filesharing.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">system-file-manager</icon>
</component>
