<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kdenetwork_filesharing</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <name>Samba Filesharing Plugin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Connector per a l'intercanvi de fitxers a Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connector per a l'intercanvi de fitxers a Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Plugin til Samba-fildeling</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Samba-Modul zur Dateifreigabe</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Πρόσθετο διαμοιρασμού αρχείων Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Samba Filesharing Plugin</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Complemento para compartir archivos con Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Samba failijagamise plugin</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Fitxategiak partekatzeko Samba plugina</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Samba-tiedostojakoliitännäinen</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Module externe de partage de fichiers Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Estensione di condivisione dei file con Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Samba 파일 공유 플러그인</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Samba failų bendrinimo papildinys</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Plug-in voor Samba bestanden delen</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Wtyczka współdzielenia plików Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">'Plugin' de Partilha de Ficheiros do Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Plugin de compartilhamento de arquivos do Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Samba Filesharing Plugin</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Samba fildelningsinsticksprogram</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Додаток оприлюднення файлів у Samba</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSamba Filesharing Pluginxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Samba 文件共享插件</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Samba 檔案分享外掛程式</name>
  <summary>Adds Configuration of Samba sharing for folders in Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Afegeix la configuració d'ús compartit de Samba al Dolphin per a les carpetes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Afig la configuració d'ús compartit de Samba al Dolphin per a les carpetes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Einrichtung von Samba-Freigaben für Ordner in Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Προσθέτει τη διαμόρφωση της κοινής χρήσης Samba για φακέλους στο Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Adds Configuration of Samba sharing for folders in Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Añade configuración para compartir carpetas con Samba en Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Samba jagamise seadistamise lisamine Dolphini kataloogidele</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Dolphinen Samba bidez karpetak partekatzeko konfigurazioa gehitzen du</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Lisää Dolphinin kansiolle Samba-jakoasetukset</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Ajoute la configuration des partages Samba pour les dossiers dans Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Aggiunge le configurazione della condivisione tramite Samba delle cartelle in Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">Dolphin에 Samba 폴더 공유 설정 추가</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Prideda Samba bendrinimo konfigūraciją aplankams Dolphin programoje</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Voegt configuratie van Samba delen van mappen toe in Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Dodaje ustawienia Samby do współdzielenia katalogów w Dolphinie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Adiciona a configuração da partilha por Samba de pastas no Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Adiciona a configuração do compartilhamento de pastas no Dolphin pelo Samba</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Pridá podporu zdieľania Samba pre priečinky v Dolphine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Lägger till inställning av delning av kataloger i Dolphin med Samba</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Додає пункти налаштовування спільного використання тек Samba у Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxAdds Configuration of Samba sharing for folders in Dolphinxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">在 Dolphin 中为文件夹添加 Samba 共享配置</summary>
  <description>
    <p>With this plugin you can set your folders to be shared on your local network using Samba, which talks the SMB protocol common on Windows and other platforms.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Amb aquest connector podreu establir les vostres carpetes perquè es comparteixin a la xarxa local usant Samba, el qual parla el protocol SMB comú al Windows i altres plataformes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Amb aquest connector podreu establir les vostres carpetes perquè es compartisquen a la xarxa local usant Samba, el qual parla el protocol SMB comú al Windows i altres plataformes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit diesem Modul können Sie Ihre Ordner in Ihrem lokalen Netzwerk freigegeben. Dazu wird Samba mit SMB-Protokoll verwendet, das auf Windows und anderen Plattformen verbreitet ist.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Με αυτό το πρόσθετο μπορείτε να ρυθμίσετε τους φακέλους σας σε κοινή χρήση με τη Samba, η οποία επικοινωνεί με το SMB πρωτόκολλο που είναι κοινό στα Windows και σε άλλες πλατφόρμες.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">With this plugin you can set your folders to be shared on your local network using Samba, which talks the SMB protocol common on Windows and other platforms.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Con este complemento puede configurar las carpetas a compartir en la red local usando Samba, que usa el protocolo SMB típico de Windows y de otras plataformas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Selle plugina abil saab määrata kindlaks kataloogid, mida soovid jagada kohtvõrgus Samba abil, mis suudab suhelda SMB protokolliga, mis on levinud Windowsis ja teistel platvormidel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Plugin honekin zure karpetak tokiko sarean Samba erabiliz partekatzeko ezar ditzakezu. Samba, Windows eta beste plataforma batzuetan ohikoa den SMB protokoloan mintzatzen da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tällä liitännäisellä voit asettaa kansiosi jaettaviksi paikallisverkossa Samballa, joka käyttää samaa SMB-yhteyskäytäntöä kuin Windows ja muut alustat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Grâce à ce module externe, vous pouvez configurer les dossiers que vous partagez sur votre réseau local à l'aide de Samba, qui permet de dialoguer en utilisant le protocole SMB avec Windows et d'autres plateformes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Con questa estensione puoi configurare le tue cartelle perché siano condivise sulla rete locale tramite Samba, che parla il protocollo SMB comune a Windows e ad altre piattaforme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 플러그인을 사용하여 Windows나 다른 플랫폼에서 자주 사용되는 SMB 프로토콜을 지원하는 Samba를 통해서 네트워크에 폴더를 공유할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Naudodami šį papildinį galite nusistatyti, kurie aplankai bus bendrinami jūsų vietiniame tinkle naudojant Samba, kuri bendrauja su Windows ir kitose platformose paplitusiu SMB protokolu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met deze plug-in kunt u uw te delen mappen op uw lokale netwerk met Samba instellen, die het SMB-protocol gebruikt wat algemeen is op Windows en andere platformen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dzięki tej wtyczce można współdzielić katalogi w sieci lokalnej przy użyciu Samby, która porozumiewa się przy użyciu protokołu SMB na Windowsie i innych platformach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Com este 'plugin', poderá configurar as suas pastas para ficarem partilhadas na sua rede local com o Samba, que por sua vez fala o protocolo SMB comum do Windows e das outras plataformas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Com este plugin você poderá configurar as suas pastas para ficarem compartilhadas na sua rede local usando o Samba, que por sua vez, utiliza o protocolo SMB comum do Windows e de outras plataformas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Pomocou tohto doplnku môžete nastaviť zdieľanie priečinkov vo vašej miestnej sieti pomocou Samby, ktorá používa protokol SMB, ktorý je bežný vo Windowse a na iných platformách.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Med det här insticksprogrammet kan du ställa in kataloger att delas på det lokala nätverket genom att använda Samba, vilket använder SMB-protokollet gemensamt med Windows och andra plattformar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою цього додатка ви можете налаштувати ваші теки на спільне використання у локальній мережі за допомогою Samba, системи обміну даними протоколом SMB, який є поширеним протоколом у Windows та на інших платформах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxWith this plugin you can set your folders to be shared on your local network using Samba, which talks the SMB protocol common on Windows and other platforms.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">使用此插件，您可以使用 Samba 设置文件夹共享到本地网络，它能与 Windows 和其他平台上的 SMB 协议通讯。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dolphin</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdenetwork-filesharing/kdenetwork-filesharing.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">system-file-manager</icon>
</component>
